techzilo.com 2019-01-30

# Privacy Policy | TechZilo

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

#### The Information We Collect

The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Name (Comments)
  * Website URl (optional) (Comments)
  * Email address (Comments)
  * Occasional polls or opinion posts
  * Google AdSense that stores tracking cookies on your computer
  * 3rd party advertisements that may store tracking cookies on your computer to recognize repeated visits (only)
  * Tracking cookies by Google Analytics for statistical purposes – this data is not traceable back to you except for your IP address
  * Google uses DART cookie which enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Visitors can opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

#### The Way We Use Information

The name and website URl are displayed on comments, but email address is secure with us. We do not share it with outside parties. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

#### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error (only from email ID that was used originally).

#### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, contact us.
